A Guide to the Trust for Mutual Understanding records FA412
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants, 1970, 1975, 1978, 1982, 1987-2012; 3; 45.95 Cubic Feet 121 letter document boxes
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, Flood Relief, EC-0214, 2002, 2006 (Box 65, Folder 726)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, B-0319, B-0403, DF-0420, 2002-2007 (Box 65, Folder 727)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, B-0319, B-0403, FCS, Photo Documentation, YVAA 2004 NYC Residency, 2005 January 13 (Box 65, Folder 727)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, Chalupecky and Oskar Cepan Awards, B-0319, B-0403, DF-0420, 2001, 2005 (Box 65, Folder 728)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, DF-0421, 2004, 2006-2007 (Box 65, Folder 729)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, EC-0501, EC-0600, 2004-2007 (Box 65, Folder 730)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, EC-0501, EC-0600, Photos for TMU, YVAA & Kosovo, 2006 (Box 65, Folder 730)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, EC-0501, EC-0600, FCS, Lala Rascic, Selected Works, 2006 September (Box 65, Folder 730)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, EC-0501, EC-0600, Lala Rascic, Slideshow, Selected Works, The Invisibles (video), Sorry Wrong Number (video), 2004-2008 (Box 65, Folder 730)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, EC-0501, EC-0600, Lala Rascic, Video Compilation, 2001-2005 (Box 65, Folder 730)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, Miscellaneous, EC-0501, EC-0600, 2004-2007 (Box 65, Folder 731)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, Miscellaneous, EC-0501, EC-0600, Lala Rascic, Works 2004-2006, Slideshow, Invisibles, Sorry Wrong Number (Box 65, Folder 731)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, Miscellaneous, EC-0501, EC-0600, Lala Rascic, Video Compilation (Box 65, Folder 731)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, Miscellaneous, EC-0501, EC-0600, YVAAA Artist Who Came to TMU, Kadri Muzai, 2006 February 9 (Box 65, Folder 731)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, Miscellaneous, EC-0501, EC-0600, Milena Putnik, Resume, Works, 2005 October (Box 65, Folder 731)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, Miscellaneous, EC-0501, EC-0600, Antun Bozicevic, It is Important to Take Part, Dom HDLU Osijek, Galerija Kazamat (Box 65, Folder 731)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, Miscellaneous, EC-0501, EC-0600, Jan Vasilico, YVAA Artists Who Came to TMU with Wendy Luers & Irena Kovarova, 2005 September 21 (Box 65, Folder 731)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, Miscellaneous, EC-0501, EC-0600, Dalibor Trencevski (Box 65, Folder 731)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, Miscellaneous, EC-0501, EC-0600, Koja (aka Fitore Isufi) (Box 65, Folder 731)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, Miscellaneous, EC-0501, EC-0600, Sinisa Ilic, Serbia (Box 65, Folder 731)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, Miscellaneous, EC-0501, EC-0600, Tina Gverovic, Croatia (Box 65, Folder 731)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, Miscellaneous, EC-0501, EC-0600, Tina Gverovic, Croatia (Box 65, Folder 731)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, Miscellaneous, EC-0501, EC-0600, 2004-2006 (Box 66, Folder 732-733)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, EC-0516, 2005-2007 (Box 66, Folder 734)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, EC-0516, Foundation for a Civil Society, TMU Board, Prague, 2005 November (Box 66, Folder 734)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, EC-0708, EC-0800, 2005, 2007-2008 (Box 66, Folder 735)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, Miscellaneous, EC-0708, EC-0800, 2007-2008 (Box 66, Folder 736)
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, EC-0708 MISC
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, EC-0708 MISC
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, EC-0708 MISC
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, EC-0708 MISC
  - Foundation for a Civil Society, EC-0708 MISC, 2012:063:021
  - Foundation fro Contemporary Arts, DF-0733, 2007-2009 (Box 66, Folder 737)
  - Foundation for Contemporary Arts, DF-0733, Foundation for Contemporary Arts, Images for TMU Annual Report (Box 66, Folder 737)
  - Foundation for International Arts & Education (FIAE), Russian Artists in America and Nukus, B-0125, 2000-2002, 2005 (Box 66, Folder 738)
  - Foundation for International Arts & Education (FIAE), B-0245, 2000, 2002-2003, 2005 (Box 67, Folder 739)
  - Foundation for International Arts & Education (FIAE), Western American Art SP2003, B-0285, 2002-2004 (Box 67, Folder 740)
  - Foundation for International Arts & Education (FIAE), Western American Art SP2003, B-0285, American Art Exhibit in Russia, 2003 April-September (Box 67, Folder 740)
  - Foundation for International Arts & Education (FIAE), B-0357, 2003-2007 (Box 67, Folder 741)
  - Foundation for International Arts & Education (FIAE), B-0415, 2004-2007 (Box 67, Folder 742)
  - Foundation for International Arts & Education (FIAE), B-0719, 2005, 2007, 2009-2010 (Box 67, Folder 743)
  - Foundation for International Arts & Education (FIAE), B-0816, 2006, 2008, 2010 (Box 67, Folder 744)
  - Foundation for Independent Artists, DF-0829, 2008 (Box 67, Folder 745)
  - Foundation for Jewish Community, DF-0123, 2001-2003, 2006-2007 (Box 67, Folder 746)
  - Foundation for Jewish Culture: LeeSaar the Company, B-0817, 2008-2009 (Box 67, Folder 747)
  - The Foundry Theatre, EC-0411, 2002-2004, 2007 (Box 68, Folder 748)
  - Fractured Atlas, Nature Theater of Oklahoma, DF-0810, 2007-2009 (Box 68, Folder 749)
  - Fractured Atlas, Nature Theater of Oklahoma, DF-0810, Photos, Croatia, Nature Theater of OK (Box 68, Folder 749)
  - Fractured Atlas, Nature Theater of Oklahoma, DF-0810, Nature Theater of Oklahoma, NO DICE, Act One, 2006 November (Box 68, Folder 749)
  - Fractured Atlas, Nature Theater of Oklahoma, DF-0810, Nature Theater of Oklahoma, NO DICE, Act Two, 2006 November (Box 68, Folder 749)
  - Franklin Furnace Archive, B-0246, 2000, 2002-2003, 2006-2007 (Box 68, Folder 750)
  - Franklin Furnace Archive, DF-0313, 20002-2003, 2005 (Box 68, Folder 751)
  - Franklin Furnace Archive, Miscellaneous, DF-0313, 2005 (Box 68, Folder 752)
  - Franklin Furnace Archive, DF-0701, 2002, 2006-2008 (Box 68, Folder 753)
  - French American Cultural Exchange, DF-0505, 2003, 2005-2006 (Box 68, Folder 754)
  - French American Cultural Exchange, DF-0505, French American Cultural Exchange, Theatre Du Soleil (Box 68, Folder 754)
  - French American Cultural Exchange, Miscellaneous, DF-0505, 2004 (Box 68, Folder 755)
  - Friends of the Earth, B-0335, 2001-2008 (Box 68, Folder 756)
  - Friends of the Bass Museum, DF-0827, 2008-2009 (Box 68, Folder 757)
  - Friends of the Bass Museum, Miscellaneous, DF-0827, 2008-2009 (Box 68, Folder 758)
  - Friends of the Budapest Festival Orchestra, DF-0823, 2007-2009 (Box 69, Folder 759)
  - Friends of the Jewish Culture Festival Society, B-0509, 2005-2006 (Box 69, Folder 760)
  - Friends of the Jewish Culture Festival Society, B-0509, Friends of the Jewish Culture Festival Society (Box 69, Folder 760)
  - Friends of the Jewish Culture Festival Society, EC-0605, 2005-2006 (Box 69, Folder 761)
  - Friends of the Jewish Culture Festival Society, EC-0605, 16th Jewish Festival, Krakow, Poland, Advertisement (Box 69, Folder 761)
  - Friends of the Jewish Culture Festival Society, Miscellaneous, EC-0605, 2006-2007, 2009 (Box 69, Folder 762)
  - Friends of the Jewish Culture Festival Society, Miscellaneous, EC-0605, 17th Jewish Festival in Krakow, Photographic Documentation, 2007 June 23-July 1 (Box 69, Folder 762)
  - Friends of the Jewish Culture Festival Society, Miscellaneous, EC-0605, 17th Jewish Festival in Krakow, Press Release, 2007 June 23-July 1 (Box 69, Folder 762)
  - Friends of the Jewish Culture Festival, Society, DF-0729, 2007-2008 (Box 69, Folder 763)
  - Friends of the Jewish Culture Festival Society, DF-0729, Friends of the Jewish Culture Festival Society, 17th Jewish Culture Festival Krakow, Poland (Box 69, Folder 763)
  - Friends of the Jewish Culture Festival Society, DF-0824, 2007-2009 (Box 69, Folder 764)
  - Friends of the Jewish Culture Festival, DF-0824, 19th Jewish Culture Festival in Krakow, Documentation for TMU (Box 69, Folder 764)
  - Friends of the Jewish Culture Festival, DF-0824, 19th Jewish Culture Festival in Krakow, Pharaoh's Daughter @The Temple Synogogue, 2009 July 1 (Box 69, Folder 764)
  - Friends of Via, DF-0644, DF-0739, 2006-2008 (Box 69, Folder 765)
  - Fund for Arts and Culture in Central and Eastern Europe, B-0126, 2001-2002 (Box 69, Folder 766)
  - Fund for Arts and Culture in Eastern and Central Europe, Russian Museum Seminars, B-0194, 2001-2002, 2007 (Box 69, Folder 767)
  - Fund for Arts and Culture in Central and Eastern Europe, Jaroslav Andel, DF-0134, 2001-2002 (Box 69, Folder 768)
  - Fund for Arts and Culture in Eastern and Central Europe, DF-0215, 2002, 2007 (Box 69, Folder 769)
  - Fund for Arts and Cultural in Central and Eastern Europe, B-0358, 2003-2005 (Box 69, Folder 770)
  - Fund for Arts and Culture in Central and Eastern Europe, B-0358, The Fund for Arts and Culture, Photographs (Box 69, Folder 770)
  - Fund for Arts and Cultural in Central and Eastern Europe, EC-0307, 2002-2003, 2007 (Box 70, Folder 771)
  - Fund for Arts and Culture in Central and Eastern Europe, EC-0307, The Fund for Arts & Culture, Digital Photographs, 2003 November 22 (Box 70, Folder 771)
  - Fund for Arts and Culture in Central and Eastern Europe, EC-0418, 2004-2006 (Box 70, Folder 772)
  - Fund for Arts and Culture in Central and Eastern Europe, Miscellaneous, EC-0418, 2004 (Box 70, Folder 773)
  - Fund for Arts and Culture in Central and Eastern Europe, B-0618, 2004-2008 (Box 70, Folder 774)
  - Fund for Arts and Culture in Central and Eastern Europe, DF-0640, 2006-2008 (Box 70, Folder 775)
  - Fund for Arts and Culture in Central and Eastern Europe, B-0720, 2006-2008 (Box 70, Folder 776)
  - Fund for Arts and Culture in Central and Eastern Europe, B-0818, 2007-2010 (Box 70, Folder 777)
  - Gamelan Son of Lion, DF-0725, 2006-2007 (Box 70, Folder 778)
  - Gamelan Son of Lion, DF-0725, Critical Mass in Krakow, 2007 June 28 (Box 70, Folder 778)
  - Gamelan Son of Lion, DF-0725, Critical Mass in Krakow, 2007 June 28 (Box 70, Folder 778)
  - The German Marshall Fund, B-0169, B-0273, B-0343, 2001-2004 (Box 70, Folder 779)
  - The German Marshall Fund, B-0169, B-0273, B-0343, 2001-2004 (Box 71, Folder 780)
  - The German Marshall Fund, Miscellaneous, B-0343, 1995, 1998-1999, 2003 (Box 71, Folder 781-783)
  - The German Marshall Fund, Environmental Partnership for Central Europe, Miscellaneous, 2002, 2002 (Box 71, Folder 784)
  - The German Marshall Fund, EC-0506, EC-0601, 2005-2006, 2008 (Box 71, Folder 785)
  - The German Marshall Fund, EC-0611, 2005-2008 (Box 71, Folder 786)
  - Give2Asia, Mongolian Museum Project, B-0147, 2001-2002, 2004 (Box 71, Folder 787)
  - Global Community Initiatives, B-0437, 2003-2006 (Box 71, Folder 788)
  - Global Forest Network, B-0226, 2001-2003, 2005-2006 (Box 72, Folder 789)
  - Global Forest Network, Miscellaneous, B-0226, 2001-2002 (Box 72, Folder 790)
  - Global Green USA, The Legacy Program, B-0170 (Box 72, Folder 791)
  - Global Green USA, B-0265, 2001-2004 (Box 72, Folder 792)
  - Global Green USA, B-0373, 2002-2005 (Box 72, Folder 793)
  - Global Green USA, B-0373, Global Green USA, CWD, St. Petersburg, Legacy Forum, Wash DC, National Dialogue, Moscow, 2004 (Box 72, Folder 793)
  - Global Green USA, B-0473, 2002, 2004-2006 (Box 72, Folder 794)
  - Global Green USA, B-0473, Global Green (Box 72, Folder 794)
  - Global Green USA, Miscellaneous, B-0473, 2005 (Box 72, Folder 795)
  - Global Green USA, EC-0419, 2002-2005, 2007-2008 (Box 72, Folder 796)
  - Global Green USA, B-0577, 2004-2008 (Box 72, Folder 797)
  - Global Green USA, B-0577, Global Green USA, Report, 2006 Grant, TMU (Box 72, Folder 797)
  - Goat Island, B-0619, 2006-2008 (Box 72, Folder 798)
  - Goat Island, Miscellaneous, B-0619, 2007-2008 (Box 72, Folder 799)
  - Goat Island, Miscellaneous, B-0619, Excerpts From: When Will September Bloom?, Last Night Was only a Comedy, A Double Performance, 2005 (Box 72, Folder 799)
  - GOH Productions, Polli Talu, B-0127, 1989, 1991-1995, 1997-2003, 2006 (Box 72, Folder 800)
  - GOH Productions, Silesian Dance Theatre, B-0128, 2000-2001, 2006-2007 (Box 73, Folder 801)
  - GOH Productions, Uzbekistan, B-0129, 1998, 2001-2002, 2006 (Box 73, Folder 802)
  - GOH Productions, Silesian Dance Theatre US Tour, B-0148, 1995, 1997, 1999-2001, 2006-2007 (Box 73, Folder 803)
  - GOH Productions, Polish Presenters, B-0195, 2001-2002, 2006 (Box 73, Folder 804)
  - GOH Productions, Silesian Dance Theater, B-0204, 2001-2003, 2007 (Box 73, Folder 805)
  - GOH Productions, B-0247, 2002-2003 (Box 73, Folder 806)
  - GOH Productions, Ilkhom Theatre US Tour, B-0286, 1991, 1995, 2001-2005 (Box 73, Folder 807)
  - GOH, Silesian Dance Theatre, EC-0308, 2003, 2006-2007 (Box 73, Folder 808)
  - GOH Productions, Brass Bands in Serbia, EC-0309, 2002-2003, 2006 (Box 73, Folder 809)
  - GOH Productions, A Page Out of Order, Supplemental, B-0631, DF-0642, 2006-2008 (Box 73, Folder 810)
  - GOH Productions, A Page Out of Order, Supplemental B-0631, DF-0642, School of Hard Knocks, Macedonia, Kyoko Hirano, Photos, 2006 (Box 73, Folder 810)
  - GOH Productions, B-0760, 2007-2008 (Box 73, Folder 811)
  - GOH Productions, B-0760, Yoshiko Chuma & The School of Hard Knocks, A Page Out of Order: M, 2007 January 15 (Box 73, Folder 811)
  - GOH Productions, DF-0714, 2007-2008 (Box 73, Folder 812)
  - Gotham Arts Exchange, B-0660, 2006-2007 (Box 73, Folder 813)
  - Government Accountability Project, DF-0124, 2000-2003, 2006 (Box 73, Folder 814)
  - Government Accountability Project, B-02104, 2002-2003, 2005-2006 (Box 73, Folder 815)
  - Government Accountability Project, DF-0445, 2000-2001, 2004-2006 (Box 74, Folder 816)
  - Government Accountability Project, Miscellaneous, DF-04445, 2004 (Box 74, Folder 817)
  - Government Accountability Project, B-0578, 2005-2006 (Box 74, Folder 818)
  - Government Accountability Project, B-0578, Government Accountability Project, Los Alamos & Russia Pictures, 2006 December 12 (Box 74, Folder 818)
  - Government Accountability Project, B-0671, 2006-2008 (Box 74, Folder 819)
  - Government Accountability Project, B-0841, 2007-2009 (Box 74, Folder 820)
  - Greenpeace Fund, Baikal Ecological Camp, B-0107, 2001-2003 (Box 74, Folder 821)
  - Greenpeace Fund, B-0227, 2001-2003 (Box 74, Folder 822)
  - Greenpeace Fund, B-0227, Discover Lake Baikal, 2002 Greenpeace Ecotourism Program (Box 74, Folder 822)
  - Greenpeace Fund, DF-0322, 2001-2003 (Box 74, Folder 823)
  - Greenpeace Fund, Miscellaneous, DF-0322, 2004 (Box 74, Folder 824)
  - Greenpeace Fund, Miscellaneous, DF-0322 (Box 74, Folder 824)
  - Greenpeace Fund, Miscellaneous, DF-0322, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 824)
  - Greenpeace Fund, Miscellaneous, DF-0322, Irkutsk Region (Box 74, Folder 824)
  - Greenpeace Fund, Miscellaneous, DF-0322, Adventure and Eco-Travel in Siberia, Baikal Is the Pearl of Siberia, Why Not Add it to Your Collection of Adventures (Box 74, Folder 824)
  - Greenpeace Fund, B-0438, 2003-2005 (Box 75, Folder 825)
  - Greenpeace Fund, B-0438, Greenpeace, Sakhalin Journalists Tour, 2005 (Box 75, Folder 825)
  - Greenpeace Fund, B-0438, Greenpeace/B-0438, Sakhalin Photos, Journalism Tour (Box 75, Folder 825)
  - Grey Art Gallery, DF-0110, 2000-2002, 2006-2007 (Box 75, Folder 826)
  - Hand 2 Mouth Theatre, DF-0419, 2003-2005, 2007 (Box 75, Folder 827)
  - Hand 2 Mouth Theatre, DF-0511, 2002-2006 (Box 75, Folder 828)
  - Hand 2 Mouth Theatre, DF-0610, 2005-2007 (Box 75, Folder 829)
  - Hand 2 Mouth Theatre, DF-0610, Hand 2 Mouth Theatre, Photos for TMU, Photos and Info Sheet (Box 75, Folder 829)
  - Hand Print Workshop International, B-0149, 2000-2003, 2006-2007 (Box 75, Folder 830)
  - Harvard School of Public Health, B-0366, 2002-2007 (Box 75, Folder 831)
  - Harvard School of Public Health, B-0336, HSPH, TMU Grant, Pictures, Moscow Trip 2006, Dioxin 2003 in Boston (Box 75, Folder 831)
  - Harvard Public School of Health, Miscellaneous, B-0336, 1999 (Box 75, Folder 832)
  - Harvard University, B-0458, 2004-2005, 2007-2008 (Box 75, Folder 833)
  - Harvestworks, EC-0510, 2005-2006 (Box 75, Folder 834)
  - Harvestworks, Violet Fire, B-0620, 2006, 2008 (Box 75, Folder 835)
  - Harvestworks "Violet FIre", B-0620, Harvestworks, Violet Fire, National Theater, Belgrade, 2006 (Box 75, Folder 835)
  - Harvestworks "Violet FIre", B-0620, Harvestworks #2, Violet Fire, National Theater, Belgrade, 2006 (Box 75, Folder 835)
  - Harvestworks, L.E.M.U.R., DF-0743, 2007-2009 (Box 75, Folder 836)
  - Harvestworks, L.E.M.U.R., DF-0743, Michael Lowenstern (Box 75, Folder 836)
  - Harvestworks, L.E.M.U.R., DF-0743, Todd Reynolds (Box 75, Folder 836)
  - Headlands Center for the Arts, B-0459, 2003-2005, 2008 (Box 76, Folder 837)
  - Headlands Center for the Arts, B-0551, B-0606, 2005-2009 (Box 76, Folder 838)
  - Headlands Center for the Arts, CCA Polish Residency Exchange, Miscellaneous, B-0606, 2006-2007 (Box 76, Folder 839)
  - Headlands Center for the Arts, B-0865, 2008-2009 (Box 76, Folder 840)
  - Headlong Dance Theater, B-0556, 2004-2008 (Box 76, Folder 841)
  - Headlong Dance Theater, B-0556, Headlong Dance Theater (Box 76, Folder 841)
  - Headlong Dance Theater, Miscellaneous, B-0556 (Box 76, Folder 842)
  - Henry Art Gallery, DF-0543, 2005-2006 (Box 76, Folder 843)
  - Heritage & Tradition, DF-0801, 2007-2008, 2012 (Box 76, Folder 844)
  - Heritage & Tradition, Miscellaneous, DF-0801, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 845)
  - Historians of German and Central European Art and Architecture, DF-0700, 2006-2008 (Box 76, Folder 846)
  - Holy Archangels Foundation, EC-0317, 2003-2004 (Box 76, Folder 847)
  - Holy Archangels Foundation, B-0416, 2003-2005, 2007-2008 (Box 76, Folder 848)
  - Hourglass Group, B-0510, 2005-2006 (Box 76, Folder 849)
  - House of Dance, DF-0125, 2000-2002 (Box 77, Folder 850)
  - House of Dance, DF-0211, 2001-2003 (Box 77, Folder 851)
  - Houston International Film Festival, DF-0120, 2001, 2007 (Box 77, Folder 852)
  - Hubbard Street Dance Chicago, B-0721, 2007-2008 (Box 77, Folder 853)
  - The Immigrants' Theatre, EC-0606, 2005-2006 (Box 77, Folder 854)
  - The Immigrants' Theatre Project, EC-0606, ITP/TMUNY, Reality and the New Romanian Theatre (Box 77, Folder 854)
  - In Parenthesis, DF-0436, 2003-2006 (Box 77, Folder 855)
  - Institute for Agriculture and Trade Policy, B-0266, 2002-2003 (Box 77, Folder 856)
  - Institute for Market Transformation, B-0743, 2006-2009 (Box 77, Folder 857)
  - The Institute for Publishing Arts, DF-0339, 2003-2005, 2007 (Box 77, Folder 858)
  - The Institute for Publishing Arts, DF-0339, Gary Mill with Polsce, Gary Mill in Poland, Mind on the Line, 2005 (Box 77, Folder 858)
  - Institute for Sustainable Communities, B-0108, 2001-2003 (Box 77, Folder 859)
  - Institute for Sustainable Communities, B-02105, 2002-2003 (Box 77, Folder 860)
  - Institute for Sustainable Communities, DF-0229, 2002-2003, 2006 (Box 77, Folder 861)
  - Institute of Visual Arts (Inova), B-0217, 2001-2002, 2007-2008 (Box 78, Folder 862)
  - Institute of Visual Arts (Inova), B-0217, Inova-Ukraine (Box 78, Folder 862)
  - Institute of Visual Arts (Inova), B-0248, 2002-2003, 2006-2008 (Box 78, Folder 863)
  - Interfaith Center of New York, DF-0226, 1999, 2002-2003, 2007 (Box 78, Folder 864)
  - Interfaith Center of New York, DF-0310, 2002-2003, 2007 (Box 78, Folder 865)
  - International Accordion Festival, B-0511, 2004-2005, 2008-2009 (Box 78, Folder 866)
  - International Accordion Festival, B-0511, International Accordion Festival (Box 78, Folder 866)
  - International Accordion Festival, B-0722, 2006-2007 (Box 78, Folder 867)
  - International Arts and Artists, DF-0834, 2005-2006. 2008-2009 (Box 78, Folder 868)
  - International Arts and Artists, Miscellaneous, DF-0834, 2008-2009 (Box 78, Folder 869)
  - International Center of Photography, DF-0101, 2000-2001, 2006 (Box 78, Folder 870)
  - International Center of Photography, B-0218, 2002-2004 (Box 78, Folder 871)
  - International Council on Monuments and Sites (ICOMOS), B-0130, 2000-2002 (Box 78, Folder 872)
  - International Council on Monuments and Sites (ICOMOS), B-0223, 2001-2003 (Box 79, Folder 873)
  - International Council on Monuments and Sites (ICOMOS), International Summer Intern Program, B-0287, 2001-2004 (Box 79, Folder 874)
  - International Council on Monuments and Sites (ICOMOS), B-0417, 2001, 2003-2004, 2006-2007 (Box 79, Folder 875)
  - International Council on Monuments and Sites (ICOMOS), B-0460, 2004-2006 (Box 79, Folder 876)
  - International Crane Foundation, B-0109, 2000-2003 (Box 79, Folder 877)
  - International Crane Foundation, B-0109, Siberian Migration, Angelo D'Arrigo, 2002 (Box 79, Folder 877)
  - International Crane Foundation, B-0232, 2001-2003 (Box 79, Folder 878)
  - International Crane Foundation, EC-0315, 2003-2004, 2006 (Box 79, Folder 879)
  - International Crane Foundation, B-0439, 2004-2006 (Box 79, Folder 880)
  - International Crane Foundation, DF-0428, 2004, 2007 (Box 80, Folder 881)
  - International Crane Foundation, B-0532, 2004-2007 (Box 80, Folder 882)
  - International Crane Foundation, B-0672, 2005-2008 (Box 80, Folder 883)
  - International Crane Foundation, B-0672, ICF Images, Projects, TMU Grants, 2007 (Box 80, Folder 883)
  - International Crane Foundation, B-0842, 2007-2009 (Box 80, Folder 884)
  - International Crane Foundation, B-0842, ICF Photos, 2008 (Box 80, Folder 884)
  - International Fund for Animal Welfare, B-0110, 2000-2003, 2005 (Box 80, Folder 885)
  - International Fund for Animal Welfare, B-0641, 2005-2008 (Box 80, Folder 886)
  - International Fund for Animal Welfare, B-0641, IFAW Report Pics, Bear Conference, 2007 May (Box 80, Folder 886)
  - International Fund for Animal Welfare, EC-0802, 2007-2009 (Box 80, Folder 887)
  - International House, B-0086, B-01115, 2000-2003, 2006 (Box 80, Folder 888)
  - International Studio and Curatorial Program (ISCP), B-0150, 2001-2002 (Box 81, Folder 889)
  - International Studio and Curatorial Program (ISCP), B-0196, 2001-2003 (Box 81, Folder 890)
  - International Studio and Curatorial Program (ISCP), Miscellaneous, B-0196, 1994, 1998-2003 (Box 81, Folder 891-892)
  - International Studio and Curatorial Program (ISCP), B-0249, 2002-2003 (Box 81, Folder 893)
  - International Studio and Curatorial Program (ISCP), B-0359, 2002-2006 (Box 81, Folder 894-895)
  - International Studio and Curatorial Program (ISCP), B-0359, ISCP Photos for TMU (Box 81, Folder 894)
  - International Studio and Curatorial Program (ISCP), B-0359, Kristina Leko, Amerika 2004-2005, Video Documentation of the Exhibition held at the Museum of Contemporary Art (Box 81, Folder 894)
  - International Studio and Curatorial Program (ISCP), B-0512, 1998-2000, 2003-2007 (Box 81, Folder 896)
  - International Studio and Curatorial Program (ISCP), B-0512, TMU 2005 from ISCP (Box 81, Folder 896)
  - International Studio and Curatorial Program (ISCP), B-0621, 1998, 2002, 2004-2008 (Box 81, Folder 897)
  - International Studio and Curatorial Program (ISCP), B-0621, TMU 06, ISCP, 2006 (Box 81, Folder 897)
  - International Studio and Curatorial Program (ISCP), B-0819, 2001, 2004, 2006-2009 (Box 82, Folder 898)
  - Interns for Peace, IFP Training Group, B-0171, 1998-2003, 2006 (Box 82, Folder 899)
  - Interns for Peace, IFP Training Group, Miscellaneous, B-0171, 1998, 2001 (Box 82, Folder 900)
  - Intersection for the Arts, B-0622, 2005-2008 (Box 82, Folder 901)
  - Inuit Circumpolar Council Alaska, B-0882, 2008-2009 (Box 82, Folder 902)
  - Inuit Circumpolar Council Alaska, B-0882, Inuit Circumpolar Conference- Alaska, Global Summit on Climate Change, Final Report (Box 82, Folder 902)
  - ISAR (Initiative for Social Action and Renewal in Eurasia), Women in Nuclear Safety Activism, B-01108, 2000-2003, 2006 (Box 82, Folder 903)
  - ISAR (Initiative for Social Action and Renewal in Eurasia), Women in Nuclear Safety Activism, Miscellaneous, B-01108, 2000-2002 (Box 82, Folder 904)